

Luis David Rosales Vázquez

Contact

1 722 56 88 358

🔀 Las Palmas, Metepec, México

Education

Academlo

Full-Stack Developer 2022-2023

UNAM

PhD in Chemistry Science 2018-2022

UAEM

Master's degree in Chemistry Science 2015-2017

UAEM

Bachelor degree in Chemistry 2010-2014

Programming

- JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, React.js, Bootstrap (1 year)
- Node.js, Pine Script (1/2 year)

About Me

I am a disciplined, self-motivated, reliable, responsible, and hard-working person. A full-stack developer ready to join a team and adaptable to all challenging situations.

Proyects

Tradingview indicators

An on-going improvement of indicators and alarms for buying and selling signals in the stock market.

 Looking and showing the optimal conditions for taking a long or shorts positions in the stock market with profits

Poke API

Responsive app with several important data of all the existing Pokemons (over a 1000).

- React. js-based application equipped with filters for a better user experience in the search for information.
- · HTML5 and CSS3 design

Rick and Morty API

Consult the origin, status, and location of all the characters of the series 'Rick and Morty'

 Search the current information for any character ever seen in the series

Weather app

Amicable application capable to detect the weather status in every city of the world

- Get the most important weather conditions of a current a current city in real-time.
- Climate-depending appearance app



Luis David Rosales Vázquez

Crece.lat

External Finantial Consultant and Teacher (partial-time) 2022-present

Teaching financial education, and helping the company with their decision-making and risk tolerance with their positions in the stock markets, allowing them to make good to great trades, and consequently, earnings.

Instituto de Quimica UNAM - CCIQS

Experience

Research assistant

2016 - 2022

Developing several metal-organic photoluminescent frameworks (chemical compounds) with high selectivity, sensitivity, and its application in toxic pollutants in water.

Fantasmas

Football coach

2016 - 2018

In charge of the defensive unit for teaching football to kids and teenagers, but more importantly, I teach the importance of discipline and how hard work pays off., winning multi times championships.

Technologies

Javascript, HTML, CSS, Node.js, Pine Script, Photoshop, Traidingview Brokers such as Interactive-Brokers, Tastyworks and Thinkorswim, Microsoft Office, Origin 8.6, Scientific Workplace, ChemOffice, ChemDraw, Mercury, TOPOS Pro, Vesta, Mestrenova, Mendeley, VESTA, Filmora.

Proyects

Ecommerce

Simulation on an e-commerce of home products.

 The application counts with features such as adding, deleting, purchase-history and buying products for a complete user experience

Atorvastatin-drug sensor

Design of a chemical luminescent sensor for atorvastatin in tablet

Cyanide-sensor

DConstruction of a chemical luminescent sensor for cyanide in water.

Skills

- · Multidisciplinary perspective (with a Scientist and Economist background)
- Problem-solving
- · Continuous learning person
- Team worker
- Leadership
- Creative